Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Domestic Advertisements, part 1, 1875-2001 and undated, bulk 1920s-1990s RL.00687
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Main Files Series, 1875-2001 and undated
  - Champion Spark Plug, 1955-1986
    - 1977-1980 (Box CS8)
    - 1981-1986 (Box CS9)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1884-1969, 1992-1994
    Proofs from the 1920s to 1950s feature testimonial advertising for Pond's Cold Cream. Noted socialites endorsing the product were photographed by well known photographers including Edward J. Steichen and Baron De Meyer.
    [See also Oversize Box OV2; Oversize Folder 11.]
    - 1884-1916 (Box CP1)
    - 1917-1920 (Box CP2)
    - 1921 (Box CP3)
    - 1922 (Box CP4)
    - 1923 (Box CP5)
    - 1924 (Box CP6)
    - 1925 (Box CP7)
    - 1925-1926 (Box CP8)
    - 1926-1928 (Box CP9)
    - 1929-1930 (Box CP10)
    - 1931 (Box CP11)
    - 1932 (Box CP12)
    - 1934-1935 (Box CP13)
    - 1936-1937 (Box CP14)
    - 1938-1939 (Box CP15)
    - 1940-1942 (Box CP16)
    - 1943-1945 (Box CP17)
    - 1946-1948 (Box CP18)
    - 1949-1951 (Box CP19)
    - 1952-1953 (Box CP20)
    - 1954-1958 (Box CP21)
    - 1959-1969, 1992-1994 (Box CP22)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific RR, 1959-1975
    - 1959-1962 (Box CH1)
    - 1963-1964 (Box CH2)
    - 1965-1966 (Box CH3)
    - 1967 (Box CH4)
    - 1968-1969 (Box CH5)
    - 1970-1975 (Box CH6)
  - Chicago Tribune, 1969-1972
    [See also Oversize Box OV3; Oversize Folder 12.]
    - 1969-1972 (Box CT1)
  - Church World Service: see Advertising Council (Box CT1)
  - Civil Defense: see Advertising Council (Box CT1)
  - Claussen Pickles: see Oscar Mayer (Box CT1)
  - Colman, JandJ: see JandJ Colman (Box CT1)
  - Columbia Presbyterian Medical Center (New York), 1955-1981
    - 1955-1962 (Box CO1)
    - 1963-1969, 1981 (Box CO2)
  - Congoleum, 1963-1979
    - 1963-1965, 1967-1971, 1974-1979 (Box CN1)
  - Crusade for Freedom: see Advertising Council (Box CN1)
  - Eastman Kodak--Consumer, 1907-1996
    Organized into two categories--Consumer and Trade advertisements--that correspond to Kodak's two major marketing areas. Consumer advertisements feature photographs by well known photographers, famous slogans and trademarks, and depict the American family over several decades in settings where the cameras are used. Introductions of new camera models are well represented, including the Instamatic in 1963, the Pocket Instamatic in 1972, the Instant camera in 1975, and the Disc camera in 1982. At different times JWT handled both film and cameras (still and/or movie) or just Kodak films. Trade advertisements include campaigns for medical and industrial films, Kodel fibers, and Eastman Chemical, as well as advertisements aimed at Kodak dealers.
    Eastman Kodak advertising is also represented in various other collections: JWT Account Files (includes films and videos plus account information); Wayne P. Ellis Collection of Kodakiana
    - ca. 1907-1915, 1930-1931 (Box EC1)
      - ca. 1907-1915 (not necessarily JWT) (Box EC1)
      - 1930 Magazine (Box EC1)
      - 1930 Newspaper (Box EC1)
      - 1930-1931 Insertion schedules, 2 folders (Box EC1)
      - 1931 Newspaper and magazine (Box EC1)
    - 1931-1932 (Box EC2)
      - 1931-1932 Magazines, 2 folders (Box EC2)
      - 1932 Insertion schedules (Box EC2)
      - ca. 1932 Death and Priceless Moments campaigns (Box EC2)
    - 1932-1933 (Box EC3)
      - 1932-1933 Magazine and newspaper, 2 folders (Box EC3)
      - 1933 Insertion schedules (Box EC3)
    - 1933-1934 (Box EC4)
      - 1933-1934 Magazines, 2 folders (Box EC4)
      - 1934 Insertion schedules (Box EC4)
    - 1934-1935 (Box EC5)
      - 1934 Insertion schedules (Box EC5)
      - 1934 Magazine (Box EC5)
      - 1934-1935 Newspaper, 2 folders (Box EC5)
    - 1935-1936 (Box EC6)
      - 1935 Magazine, 2 folders (Box EC6)
      - 1936 Insertion schedules (Box EC6)
      - 1936 Newspaper (Box EC6)
    - 1936-1937 (Box EC7)
      - 1936-1937 Kodak, 2 folders (Box EC7)
      - 1937 Insertion schedules (Box EC7)
    - 1937-1938 (Box EC8)
      - 1937 Kodak (Box EC8)
      - 1937-1938 Tennessee Eastman Corporation (Tenite) (Box EC8)
      - 1938 Home movie cameras (Box EC8)
      - 1938 Insertion schedules (Box EC8)
      - 1938 Photographs, cameras (Box EC8)
    - 1938-1939 (Box EC9)
      - 1938-1939 Kodascope Library Division (Box EC9)
      - 1939 Home movie cameras (Box EC9)
      - 1939 Insertion schedules (Box EC9)
      - 1939 Photographs, cameras (Box EC9)
    - 1940 (Box EC10)
      - 1940 Home movie cameras (Box EC10)
      - 1940 Insertion schedules (Box EC10)
      - 1940 Newspaper (Box EC10)
      - 1940 Photographs, cameras (Box EC10)
    - 1941-1942 (Box EC11)
      - 1941-1942 Home movie cameras, 2 folders (Box EC11)
      - 1941-1942 Insertion schedules, 2 folders (Box EC11)
      - 1941-1942 Photographs, cameras, 2 folders (Box EC11)
      - 1942 Newspaper (Box EC11)
    - 1943-1944 (Box EC12)
      - 1943-1944 Home movie cameras (Box EC12)
      - 1943-1944 Industrial photography (wartime) (Box EC12)
      - 1943-1944 Insertion schedules, 2 folders (Box EC12)
      - 1943-1944 Newspaper (Box EC12)
      - 1943-1944 Photographs, cameras, film (wartime advertisements), 2 folders (Box EC12)
    - 1945-1946 (Box EC13)
      - 1945 Home movie cameras (Box EC13)
      - 1945-1946 Insertion schedules, 2 folders (Box EC13)
      - 1945-1946 Photography, cameras, film, 2 folders (Box EC13)
    - 1946-1948 (Box EC14)
      - 1946-1948 Home movie cameras, projectors, 2 folders (Box EC14)
      - 1947 Photography, cameras, film (Box EC14)
      - 1947-1948 Insertion schedules, 2 folders (Box EC14)
    - 1948-1949 (Box EC15)
      - 1948 Photography, cameras, Kodachrome film, 2 folders (Box EC15)
      - 1948-1949 Insertion schedules (Box EC15)
      - 1948-1949 Newspaper (Box EC15)
    - 1949-1950 (Box EC16)
      - 1949 Home movie cameras, projectors (Box EC16)
      - 1949-1950 Photography, cameras, Kodachrome film, 3 folders (Box EC16)
    - 1950-1953 (Box EC17)
      - 1950 Insertion schedules (Box EC17)
      - 1950-1953 Home movie cameras, projectors, 3 folders (Box EC17)
      - 1951-1953 Photography, cameras, Kodachrome film, 2 folders (Box EC17)
    - 1953-1954 (Box EC18)
      - 1953-1954 Newspaper, 2 folders (Box EC18)
    - 1954-1955 (Box EC19)
      - 1954 Photography, cameras, Kodachrome film (Box EC19)
      - 1954-1955 Home movie cameras, projectors (Box EC19)
      - 1955 Newspaper (Box EC19)
    - 1955-1957 (Box EC20)
      - 1955-1956 Photography, cameras, Kodachrome film, 2 folders (Box EC20)
      - 1956 Home movie cameras, projectors (Box EC20)
      - 1956 T.V. Guide advertisements for Kodak-sponsored programs (Box EC20)
    - 1956-1957 (Box EC21)
      - 1956-1957 Newspaper (Box EC21)
      - 1956-1957 Photography at Work campaign (Box EC21)
    - 1957-1958 (Box EC22)
      - 1957 Home movie cameras, projectors (Box EC22)
      - 1957 Photography, cameras, accessories (Box EC22)
      - 1957-1958 Newspaper (Box EC22)
    - 1958-1959 (Box EC23)
      - 1958-1959 Home movie cameras, projectors (Box EC23)
      - 1958-1959 Photography at Work campaign (Box EC23)
      - 1958-1959 Photography, cameras, accessories, 2 folders (Box EC23)
      - 1959 Insertion schedules (Box EC23)
      - 1959 Newspaper (Box EC23)
    - 1960-1961 (Box EC24)
      - 1960 Home movie cameras, projectors (Box EC24)
      - 1960 Insertion schedules (Box EC24)
      - 1960 Newspaper (Box EC24)
      - 1960-1961 Photography, cameras, accessories, 2 folders (Box EC24)
    - 1961-1963 (Box EC25)
      - 1961-1962 Home movie cameras, projectors (Box EC25)
      - 1961-1963 Newspaper (Box EC25)
      - 1962-1963 Photography, cameras, Kodachrome II film, 2 folders (Box EC25)
      - 1963 Global advertising campaign (Box EC25)
        Reader's Digest inserts in multiple languages.
    - 1964-1966 (Box EC26)
      - 1964 Photography, cameras, Kodachrome II film (Box EC26)
      - 1964-1965 Kodak Pavilion (World's Fair) (Box EC26)
      - 1964-1966 Newspaper (Box EC26)
      - 1965-1966 Home movie cameras, projectors (Box EC26)
    - 1965-1967 (Box EC27)
      - 1965-1967 Photography, cameras, accessories, 3 folders (Box EC27)
        Includes Instamatic cameras.
      - 1967 Global advertising campaigns (Box EC27)
      - 1967 Newspaper and magazine (Box EC27)
        Includes home movie cameras, projectors, Instamatic.
    - 1968-1970 (Box EC28)
      - 1968-1969 Global advertising campaigns, 2 folders (Box EC28)
      - 1968-1970 Home movie cameras, projectors (Box EC28)
      - 1968-1970 Newspaper (Box EC28)
      - 1968-1970 Photography, cameras, film, 2 folders (Box EC28)
    - 1971-1972 (Box EC29)
      - 1971 Global advertising campaigns (Box EC29)
      - 1971 Newspaper (Box EC29)
      - 1971-1972 Home movie cameras, projectors (Box EC29)
      - 1971-1972 Photography, Instamatic cameras, film (Box EC29)
      - 1972 Introducing the Pocket Instamatic (Box EC29)
    - 1972-1974 (Box EC30)
      - 1972-1973 Newspaper (Box EC30)
      - 1972-1974 Black models featured (Box EC30)
      - 1973-1974 Instamatic Pocket camera (Box EC30)
      - 1973-1974 Photography, Instamatic cameras, film (Box EC30)
      - 1973-1974 Sound movie cameras, projectors (Box EC30)
      - 1974 More Than a Business campaign (Box EC30)
    - 1974-1976 (Box EC31)
      - 1974-1975 Newspaper (Box EC31)
      - 1975 More Than a Business campaign (Box EC31)
      - 1975-1976 Black models featured (Box EC31)
      - 1975-1976 Instamatic cameras (Box EC31)
      - 1975-1976 Photography, cameras, film (Box EC31)
      - 1975-1976 Sound movie cameras, projectors (Box EC31)
    - 1976-1977 (Box EC32)
      - 1976 Newspaper (Box EC32)
        Including Spanish-language advertisements.
      - 1977 Black models featured (Box EC32)
      - 1977 Photography, cameras, film (Box EC32)
      - 1977 Sound movie cameras, projectors (Box EC32)
    - 1977-1979 (Box EC33)
      - 1977-1978 Military (Box EC33)
      - 1977-1979 Newspaper (Box EC33)
      - 1978-1979 Black models featured (Box EC33)
      - 1978-1979 Instamatic cameras (Box EC33)
      - 1978-1979 Photography, cameras, film (Box EC33)
      - 1978-1979 Sound movie cameras, projectors (Box EC33)
    - 1980-1990 (Box EC34)
      - 1980 Black models featured (Box EC34)
      - 1980-1982 Sound movie cameras, projectors (Box EC34)
      - 1980-1984 Instamatic cameras (Box EC34)
        Introducing the Disc camera.
      - 1980-1984 Newspaper (Box EC34)
      - 1980-1990 Photography, cameras, film, 3 folders (Box EC34)
    - 1986-1996 (Box EC35)
      - 1986-1996 Consumer, 10 folders (Box EC35)
  - Eastman Kodak--Trade, 1931-1993
    This category provides extensive documentation of the trade oriented advertisements from the Eastman Kodak Company from 1931-1990. Although formal division titles changed slightly throughout the company's history, general markets consistently advertised include:
    Medical, including dental and radiography; chemical, including chemicals, plastics, and cellulose divisions; business reproductions, including Recordak; Tennessee Eastman, including Eastman Chemicals and Eastman Fibers (Kodel); industrial photography, including engineering and functional photography; motion pictures; business premiums; and pharmaceutical trade, probably the least represented.
    International advertisements may be found as early as 1961 randomly included and continuing throughout the collection for various years. The majority of advertisements are proofs; very few tearsheets appear. Prior to the 1960s, the physical condition of the advertisements varies from poor to good with many advertisements still attached to black scrapbook paper. The remaining advertisements were not initially stored in the scrapbooks; therefore, they range from good to very good physical condition. The quantity for any given year varies somewhat; however, the following years have a minimal number of advertisements: 1966-1967, 1970, 1972-1973.
    [See also Oversize Box OV4.]
    - 1931 (Box ET1)
      - 1931 Chemical Division (Box ET1)
      - 1931 Insertion schedules (Box ET1)
      - 1931 Medical Division and radio talks (Box ET1)
      - 1931 Pharmaceutical trade (Box ET1)
      - 1931 Teaching films (Box ET1)
    - 1931-1933 (Box ET2)
      - 1931-1933 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET2)
      - 1931-1933 Recordak (Box ET2)
      - 1932 Medical Division (Box ET2)
      - 1932-1933 Chemical Division (Box ET2)
      - 1932-1933 Pharmaceutical trade (Box ET2)
    - 1933-1935 (Box ET3)
      - 1933-1934 Medical Division, 2 folders (Box ET3)
      - 1933-1935 Teaching films (Box ET3)
      - 1934-1935 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET3)
      - 1934-1935 Recordak (Box ET3)
    - 1934-1936 (Box ET4)
      - 1934-1936 Chemical Sales Division (Box ET4)
      - 1934-1936 Pharmaceutical trade (Box ET4)
      - 1935 Medical Division (Box ET4)
      - 1936 Insertion schedule (Box ET4)
      - 1936 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET4)
    - 1936-1938 (Box ET5)
      - 1936-1937 Medical Division (Box ET5)
      - 1936-1938 Recordak (Box ET5)
      - 1936-1938 Teaching films (Box ET5)
      - 1936-1938 Tennessee Eastman Corporation (Box ET5)
        Includes Eastman acetate yarn (Teca)
      - 1937 Chemical Division (Box ET5)
      - 1937 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET5)
      - 1937-1938 Insertion schedules, 2 folders (Box ET5)
      - 1937-1938 Pharmaceutical trade (Box ET5)
    - 1938-1940 (Box ET6)
      - 1938-1939 Chemical Division (acetate sheet) (Box ET6)
      - 1938-1939 Medical Division (Box ET6)
      - 1938-1940 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET6)
      - 1939-1940 Classroom films (Box ET6)
      - 1939-1940 Insertion schedules, 2 folders (Box ET6)
      - 1939-1940 Pharmaceutical trade (Box ET6)
      - 1939-1940 Recordak (Box ET6)
    - 1940-1941 (Box ET7)
      - 1940 Medical Division (Box ET7)
      - 1940-1941 Chemical Sales Division, 2 folders (Box ET7)
      - 1940-1941 Tennessee Eastman (Eastman acetate) (Box ET7)
      - 1941 Insertion schedules (Box ET7)
    - 1941-1942 (Box ET8)
      - 1941-1942 Medical Division (Box ET8)
      - 1941-1942 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET8)
      - 1941-1942 Recordak (Box ET8)
      - 1941-1942 Pharmaceutical and photographic trade (Box ET8)
      - 1941-1942 Teaching films (Box ET8)
      - 1942 Industrial (X-Ray Division) (Box ET8)
      - 1942 Insertion schedules (Box ET8)
    - 1942-1943 (Box ET9)
      - 1942 V-Mail (Box ET9)
      - 1942-1943 Chemical Division (Box ET9)
      - 1942-1943 Tennessee Eastman Corporation (Box ET9)
      - 1943 Industrial Division (X-Ray Division) (Box ET9)
      - 1943 Insertion schedules (Box ET9)
      - 1943 Teaching films (Box ET9)
    - 1943-1945 (Box ET10)
      - 1943-1944 Medical Division (Box ET10)
      - 1943-1944 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET10)
      - 1943-1944 Pharmaceutical and photographic trade (Box ET10)
      - 1943-1944 Recordak (Box ET10)
      - 1944 Insertion schedules (Box ET10)
      - 1944-1945 Eastman Corporation (Tennessee Eastman) (Box ET10)
    - 1944-1945 (Box ET11)
      - 1944-1945 Industrial Division (X-Ray Division) (Box ET11)
      - 1944-1945 Research laboratories (Box ET11)
      - 1944-1945 Teaching films (Box ET11)
      - 1945 Medical Division (Box ET11)
      - 1945 Insertion schedules (Box ET11)
      - 1945 Pharmaceutical and Photographic Division (Box ET11)
      - 1945 Photo layouts, photo visuals, radiography, transfax (Box ET11)
      - 1945 Recordak (Box ET11)
      - 1945 Wartime motion pictures (Box ET11)
    - 1946-1947 (Box ET12)
      - 1946 Functional photography (spectroscopy, photomicrography) (Box ET12)
      - 1946 Insertion schedules (Box ET12)
      - 1946 Medical Division (Box ET12)
      - 1946 Recordak (Box ET12)
      - 1946-1947 Cellulose Products Sales Division (Box ET12)
        Includes Eastman acetate sheets, Kodapak.
      - 1946-1947 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET12)
    - 1946-1947 (Box ET13)
      - 1946-1947 Pharmaceutical, photographic and projectionist trades (Box ET13)
      - 1946-1947 Radiography (Box ET13)
      - 1946-1947 Teaching films (Box ET13)
      - 1946-1947 Transfax (Box ET13)
      - 1947 Medical Division (Box ET13)
    - 1947 (Box ET14)
      - 1947 Industrial Division (functional photography) (Box ET14)
      - 1947 Insertion schedules (Box ET14)
      - 1947 Kodagraph autopositive paper (Box ET14)
      - 1947 Recordak (Box ET14)
    - 1948 (Box ET15)
      - 1948 Functional photography (Box ET15)
      - 1948 Insertion schedules (Box ET15)
      - 1948 Motion picture trade (Box ET15)
      - 1948 Recordak (Box ET15)
      - 1948 Training and promotional films (Box ET15)
    - 1948-1949 (Box ET16)
      - 1948-1949 Insertion schedules (Box ET16)
      - 1948-1949 Medical Division (Box ET16)
      - 1948-1949 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET16)
      - 1948-1949 Recordak (Box ET16)
    - 1948-1949 (Box ET17)
      - 1948-1949 Cellulose Division (Kodapak) (Box ET17)
      - 1948-1949 Kodagraph autopositive paper (Box ET17)
      - 1948-1949 Medical Division (Box ET17)
    - 1949-1952 (Box ET18)
      - 1949 Functional photography (radiography) (Box ET18)
      - 1950 Insertion schedules (Box ET18)
      - 1950-1952 Cellulose Division (Kodapak) (Box ET18)
      - 1950-1952 Kodagraph autopositive paper and contact paper (Box ET18)
      - 1950-1952 Motion picture trade (Box ET18)
      - 1951-1952 Training and promotional films (Box ET18)
    - 1951-1952 (Box ET19)
      - 1951-1952 Functional photography (radiography) (Box ET19)
      - 1951-1952 Medical Division (Box ET19)
      - 1951-1952 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET19)
      - 1951-1952 Recordak (Box ET19)
      - 1952 Pharmaceutical trade (Box ET19)
    - 1953-1955 (Box ET20)
      - 1953 Industrial Photographic Division (Kodagraph) (Box ET20)
      - 1953 Recordak (Box ET20)
      - 1953-1955 Medical Division (Box ET20)
      - 1953-1955 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET20)
    - 1953-1955 (Box ET21)
      - 1953-1955 Cellulose Division (Kodapak) (Box ET21)
      - 1953-1955 Functional photography (radiography) (Box ET21)
      - 1953-1955 Motion Picture Division (Box ET21)
      - 1953-1955 Photography at Work campaign (Box ET21)
      - 1954 Recordak (Box ET21)
    - 1954-1955 (Box ET22)
      - 1954-1955 Industrial Photographic Division (Box ET22)
        Includes Business Photo Methods Division-Verifax, Graphic Reproduction Division-Kodagraph reproduction materials.
      - 1954-1955 Pharmaceutical and photographic trade (Box ET22)
      - 1955 Recordak (Box ET22)
    - 1956-1957 (Box ET23)
      - 1956 Recordak, 2 folders (Box ET23)
      - 1956-1957 Cellulose Products Division (Kodapak) (Box ET23)
      - 1956-1957 Medical Division (Box ET23)
    - 1956-1957 (Box ET24)
      - 1956-1957 Advertisement--Trade (Box ET24)
      - 1956-1957 Business Photo Methods Division (Verifax) and Graphic Reproduction Division (Kodapak) (Box ET24)
      - 1956-1957 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET24)
      - 1956-1957 Motion Picture Division (Box ET24)
      - 1956-1957 X-Ray Division (radiography) (Box ET24)
    - 1957-1959 (Box ET25)
      - 1957 Recordak (Box ET25)
      - 1958 Recordak and Verifax (Box ET25)
      - 1958-1959 Advertisement and pharmaceutical trade (Box ET25)
      - 1958-1959 Cellulose Products Division (Kodapak) (Box ET25)
      - 1958-1959 Motion Picture Division (Box ET25)
      - 1958-1959 X-Ray Division (radiography) (Box ET25)
    - 1958-1960 (Box ET26)
      - 1958-1960 Graphic Reproduction Division (Kodapak) (Box ET26)
      - 1958-1960 Medical Division (Box ET26)
        Includes Spanish-language advertisements.
      - 1958-1960 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET26)
      - 1959 Insertion schedules (Box ET26)
      - 1959 Recordak, Verifax, Ektalith (Box ET26)
      - 1960 Business premiums (Box ET26)
      - 1960 Functional photography (Box ET26)
    - 1960-1964 (Box ET27)
      - 1960 Cellulose Products Division (Box ET27)
      - 1960 Insertion schedules (Box ET27)
      - 1960 Motion Picture Division (Box ET27)
      - 1960 Recordak, Verifax (Box ET27)
      - 1960, 1962-1964 X-Ray Division, Engineering, 2 folders (Box ET27)
      - 1961-1963 Kodak premiums (Box ET27)
      - 1961-1963 Kodak sound recording system (Box ET27)
      - 1961-1964 International (Box ET27)
      - 1963-1964 Travel trade (Box ET27)
    - 1964-1965 (Box ET28)
      - 1964 Recordak (Box ET28)
      - 1964-1965 Kodak premiums (Box ET28)
      - 1964-1965 Kodak sound recording system (Box ET28)
      - 1964-1965 Medical Division (Box ET28)
      - 1964-1965 Medical Division (dental) (Box ET28)
      - 1964-1965 Motion Picture Division (Box ET28)
      - 1964-1965 Photo Reproductions Products Division (Box ET28)
        Includes Kodagraph, Extalith, Kodastar.
      - 1964-1965 Tennessee Eastman (Box ET28)
        Includes Plastic Sheeting Division (Uvex, Kodar), Eastman Chemical Products (Baler Twine).
    - 1965-1970 (Box ET29)
      - 1965 Copiers (Recordak, X-OMAT) (Box ET29)
      - 1965-1966 Radiography Markets Division and Engineering (Box ET29)
      - 1965-1969 International Marketing Division (Box ET29)
      - 1966 Kodak sound recording system (Box ET29)
      - 1966-1967 Recordak (Box ET29)
      - 1966, 1968-1969 Motion Picture and Education Markets Division (Box ET29)
        Includes Eastman Ektachrome film.
      - 1966-1970 Kodak premiums (Box ET29)
    - 1967-1971 (Box ET30)
      - 1967-1970 Engineering, Eastman industrial films (Box ET30)
      - 1967-1971 Radiography Markets Division (Box ET30)
      - 1968-1969 Recordak (Box ET30)
      - 1968-1969, 1971 Eastman Chemical Products (Tennessee Eastman) (Box ET30)
      - 1968-1970 Business Systems Markets Division (Box ET30)
    - 1971-1973 (Box ET31)
      - 1971 Tennessee Eastman, Eastman Chemical Products (Kodel), 2 folders (Box ET31)
      - 1971-1972 Kodak business premiums (Box ET31)
      - 1971-1973 Business Systems Markets Division (Box ET31)
        Includes Kodak microfilm systems, Kodagraph film.
    - 1972-1975 (Box ET32)
      - 1972-1974 Tennessee Eastman, Eastman Chemical Products (Kodel) (Box ET32)
      - 1972-1975 Customer Equipment Services Division (Box ET32)
      - 1973-1975 Eastman premiums (Box ET32)
      - 1974 International Photographic Division (Box ET32)
      - 1974-1975 Chemical Products Division (Box ET32)
      - 1974-1975 Radiography (Box ET32)
    - 1974-1977 (Box ET33)
      - 1974-1976 Business Systems Markets Division (Box ET33)
      - 1974-1977 Motion Picture Division (Box ET33)
      - 1974-1977 Newspaper advertisements (Box ET33)
      - 1975 Tennessee Eastman, Eastman Chemical Products (Kodel) (Box ET33)
      - 1976-1977 Customer Equipment Services Division (Technical sales representatives) (Box ET33)
      - 1976-1977 Microfilm (Box ET33)
    - 1976-1979 (Box ET34)
      - 1976-1977 Business Systems Markets Division (Box ET34)
        Including Graphics Markets Division.
      - 1976-1979 Radiography, 2 folders (Box ET34)
      - 1976-1983 Kodak premiums (Box ET34)
      - 1977 Pharmaceutical trade (Box ET34)
      - 1978-1979 Motion Picture Division (Box ET34)
    - 1978-1993 (Box ET35)
      - 1978, 1980-1981 Industrial film (Box ET35)
      - 1978-1982 Graphics Markets Division (Box ET35)
      - 1978-1982, 1984 Newspaper advertisements (Box ET35)
      - 1980-1982 Radiography (Box ET35)
      - 1980-1984, 1987 Motion Picture Division, 2 folders (Box ET35)
      - 1983-1984, 1987-1990 Radiography, health sciences, and clinical products (Box ET35)
      - 1983-1989 Graphics Systems Division (copy products) (Box ET35)
      - 1987-1989 Ultra technologies (Box ET35)
      - 1988-1989 Mass memory products (Box ET35)
        Includes Business imaging systems, computer printers.
  - Eaton Corporation, 1971-1990
    - 1971-1982, 1985-1986, 1989-1990 (Box EA1)
  - Eli Lilly, 1968-1993